Guide to the Jimenez Family Papers TAM.838
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Jimenez Family Papers
1934-2007
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Jimenez, Mona
Jimenez Family
Jimenez Tegeda, Michael A. (Michael Angelo)
Jimenez, Mary Rachel Walton
TAM.838
.75 Linear Feet in 1 manuscript box and 1 half manuscript box
The Jimenez Family is a Spanish American family based in New York. Michael "Mike" Angelo Jimenez (also known as Miguel Angel Jimenez Tejeda, abbreviated as MAJ) was born in the United States, and moved to Spain in 1934 with his family. He served in the Spanish Army, and later the International Brigades during the Spanish Civil War. He was incarcerated in forced labor and prisoner of war camps (Camp of Septfonds and Gur) until he escaped and returned to the United States in 1940. He served in the United States Army and the Office of Strategic Services (OSS). Mike later organized and worked with the United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America (UE) and the International Association of Machinists (IAM) in upstate New York, during which he negotiated the reorganization of UE locals into the IAM. He later left the IAM due to political persecution. Mary Rachel (Walton) Jimenez (abbreviated as MRW or MWJ) was an artist, art educator, and activist. She studied at the Art Student League, and was a member of the Vagabond Puppeteers Troupe, who performed in solidarity with the Dairy Farmers Union during their 1939 strike. During World War II, Mary worked in the shipyards of Chester, Pennsylvania as a welder, and was an active member of the International Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America. The Jimenez Family Papers (dated 1934-2007) consists of materials created and collected by members of the Jimenez Family, with particular emphasis on Michael "Mike" Angelo Jimenez and Mary Walton and the ways their lives intersected around political activities. The collection documents Mike's participation in the Spanish Army and later the International Brigades, including a diary from his crossing of the Pyrenees in February 1939. Other materials include photographs and records of him being imprisoned in French camps for combatants, and the family's efforts to safely transport Mike and his siblings to the United States. The collection also includes materials documenting Mike's advocacy within the United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America (UE) and the International Association of Machinists (IAM) in upstate New York, as well as his departure from the IAM as a result of the political repression and persecution of radical and leftist individuals during the mid-20th century. Mary's records demonstrate her life as an accomplished artist and her radical politics. Letters by Mary during World War II, during which she worked in the shipyards in Chester, Pennsylvania and was active in the International Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America, provides a critical perspective of a woman working (and organizing) within the union, and documents efforts for organizing between Black and white workers across the shipyard. Family photographs and the correspondence between Mike and Mary during World War II further documents their personal lives. While much of the collection concerns Mike and Mary's lives, the collection also includes materials documenting Manuel Jimenez Romance (Mike's father) during the Spanish Civil War through letters to friends and family, photographs, and research files.
Scope and Contents
The Jimenez Family Papers (dated 1934-2007) consists of materials created and collected by members of the Jimenez Family, with particular emphasis on Michael "Mike" Angelo Jimenez and Mary Rachel (Walton) Jimenez, and the ways their lives intersected around political activities. The collection documents Mike's participation in the Spanish Army and later the International Brigades, including a diary from his crossing of the Pyrenees in February 1939. Other materials include photographs and records of him being imprisoned in French camps for combatants, and the family's efforts to safely transport Mike and his siblings to the United States. The collection also includes materials documenting Mike's advocacy within the United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America (UE) and the International Association of Machinists (IAM) in upstate New York, as well as his departure from the IAM as a result of the political repression and persecution of radical and leftist individuals during the mid-20th century. Mary's records demonstrate her life as an accomplished artist and her radical politics. Letters by Mary during World War II, during which she worked in the shipyards in Chester, Pennsylvania and was active in the International Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America, provides a critical perspective of a woman working and organizing within the union, and documents efforts for organizing between Black and white workers across the shipyard. Family photographs and the correspondence between Mike and Mary during World War II further documents their personal lives. While much of the collection concerns Mike and Mary's lives, the collection also includes materials documenting Manuel Jimenez Romance (Mike's father) during the Spanish Civil War through letters to friends and family, photographs, and research files.
Arrangement
This collection has not been arranged by an archivist. The materials are arranged chronologically in the order in which they were received from the donor.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by Mona Jimenez, the daughter of Mike and Mary Jimenez, in June 2024; the accession number associated with this gift is 2024.038.
Appraisal
The following materials were excluded from the collection and remain with the Jiménez Family: select letters from Mary Jiménez, pre-Spain Jiménez family records, and records such as passports, birth certificates, and marriage certificates.
Historical Note
The Jimenez Family is a Spanish American family based in New York.
Michael "Mike" Angelo Jimenez (also known as Miguel Angel Jimenez Tejeda, abbreviated as MAJ) was born in the United States, and moved to Spain in 1934 with his family. He served in the Spanish Army, and later the International Brigades during the Spanish Civil War. He was incarcerated in forced labor and prisoner of war camps (Camp of Septfonds and Gur) until he escaped and returned to the United States in 1940. He served in the United States Army and the Office of Strategic Services (OSS). Mike later organized and worked with the United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America (UE) and the International Association of Machinists (IAM) in upstate New York, during which he negotiated the reorganization of UE locals into the IAM. He later left the IAM due to political persecution.
Mary Rachel (Walton) Jimenez (abbreviated as MRW or MWJ) was an artist, art educator, and activist. She studied at the Art Student League, and was a member of the Vagabond Puppeteers Troupe, who performed in solidarity with the Dairy Farmers Union during their 1939 strike. During World War II, Mary worked in the shipyards of Chester, Pennsylvania as a welder, and was an active member of the International Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America.
Other members of the Jimenez Family represented in the collection include: Rose [Foster Avery] Walton, Mary's mother (RFW)
Manuel Jimenez Romance, Michael's father. The last name is in Spanish form of father's last name followed by mother's last name (MJR). Manuel was a member of the Unión General de Trabajadores (UGT, General Union of Workers) trade union in Spain, and during the Spanish Civil War, was forced with one son, Daniel, into a refugee camp for non-combatants in France in 1939.
Herminia Tejeda Jimenez, Michael's mother. The last name is in American form: first name, maiden name, married name. Herminia's mother's name is unverified so originally known as Herminia Tejeda. However in some documents known as Herminia Tejeda Troncoso (HTJ)
Manuel Jimenez Tejeda (also known as James or Jim Jimenez Tejeda), Michael's brother. The last name is in Spanish form of father's last name followed by mother's last name. (MJT)
Antonio Daniel Jimenez Tejeda (also known as Daniel or Danny Jimenez Tejeda). Michael's brother. The last name is in Spanish form of father's last name followed by mother's last name. (AJT)
José Jimenez Tejeda (also known as Joseph or Joe Jimenez Tejeda). Michael's brother. The last name is in Spanish form of father's last name followed by mother's last name. (JJT)
Juan Isidro Jimenez Tejeda (also known as John or Johnny Jimenez Tejeda). Michael's brother. The last name is in Spanish form of father's last name followed by mother's last name (JIJT)
Delores Jimenez Tejeda (also known as Delores or Lola Jimenez Tejeda). Michael's sister. The last name is in Spanish form of father's last name followed by mother's last name. Later Delores Gleaton (DJG) (DJT)
Fernando Jimenez Tejeda (also known as Fernando or Nando Jimenez Tejeda). Michael's brother. The last name is in Spanish form of father's last name followed by mother's last name. (FJT)
Other Finding Aids
Many letters have been individually summarized by the donor; this description is available through the collection file by request.
Spain -- History -- Civil War, 1936-1939.; Correspondence.; Labor union members.; Women labor union members -- United States.; World War, 1939-1945 -- Correspondence.; Labor movement -- New York (State); Jimenez, Mona
- Jimenez, Mary Rachel Walton -- Mexico Trip Documents, Prints, Photographs, 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Photos, Thumbnails of Artworks and Two Small Block Prints – Mexico Trip with Jerry Oberwager, 1937-1938
  - Promotional Cards for Speaker Series at the Palacio de Bellas Artes, Mexico, under the Auspices of American Friends of the Mexican People, circa 1937-1938
- Jimenez, Mary Rachel Walton -- Mexico Correspondence, 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Letter MRW-Walton Family, 1937-06-07
  - Letter MRW-RFW, 1937-06-23
  - Letter MRW- RFW, 1938-06-07
- Jimenez Tejeda Family -- Spain and France, 1934-1940 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Letter MJR-CA Department of Motor Vehicles and Reply Concerning Documentation of Chauffeur's License, 1934-06-30
  - MJR Member ID for Unión General de la Trabajadores (UGT), 1937-01-02
  - MJR Membership Card for Unión General de la Trabajadores (UGT), 1937-1939
  - MJR ID from Oficina de Col•locacío Obrera de Barcelona, 1935-01-08
  - Memo re: HTJ Stay in Hospital de la Santa Cruz y San Pablo and Ailments, 1939-05-30
  - HTJ Description of Cause of Death, 1939-07-02
  - Telegram MJT-MJR re: Death of HTJ, 1939-07-01
  - Death Certificate Ville de Dole, France for Manuel Jimenez Romance, died 1940-02-24, 1940-03-09
  - Telegram ADJ-MAJ re: Death of MJR, 1940-02-25
  - Receipt Francisco Burlo Ventura to MJT & AJT re: furniture at Calle Entenza, No. 103 to Satisfy Debts, 1940-07-09
- Jimenez Tejeda, Michael A. -- Spanish Civil War Military Documents, 1936-1939 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 10 Postcards PSU-UGT, 1936-1939
  - MAJ Business Card for Plaza Radio Company, London, New York, Barcelona, 1934-1936
  - MAJ UGT IDs re: Sección Radiotelegrafia, 1934-1939
  - MAJ Military Training Certificate, 1937-12-15
  - MAJ International Brigades Carnet Militar, 1937-1939
  - MAJ Military Instructions, 1937-10-11
  - MAJ Military Instructions, 1938-01-29
  - MAJ Military Instructions, 1838-02-06
  - MAJ Military Instructions Grupo Central de Transmisiones, 1938-11-30
  - MAJ Military Instructions, 1938-12-02
  - MAJ Military Instructions, 1938-12-19
  - MAJ Promotion to Capitan, 1938-09-06
  - MAJ Military Identity Cards, 1938-1939
  - MAJ Military Instructions, 1939-01-09
  - MAJ Military Instructions, 1939-01-21
  - MAJ Military Instructions, 1939-02-03
  - MAJ Military Instructions, 1939-02-07
- Jimenez Tejeda, Michael A. -- Spanish Civil War Camps, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - MAJ Journal from Portbou, Spain to France, 1939
  - Statement by MAJ of Conditions at the Concentration Camp (Camp de Gurs, France), 1939
  - Letter from George M. Abbott (State Department), Marseille to MAJ while in Concentration Camp (La Barcares, France) re: Passport, 1939-04-15
  - Letter from Abbott to MAJ in French, 1939-04-15
  - Letter from W. Perry George (State Department), Bordeaux to MAJ while in Concentration Camp (Camp de Gurs, France) re: Holding Passport and Funds Needed for Passage, 1939-05-04
  - Certificate of Vaccination for MAJ at Camp de Gurs, 1939-06
  - Letter from William D. Moreland, Jr. (State Department), Bordeaux to MAJ, Camp de Septfonds Offering Appointment, 1939-07-13
  - Certificate of Vaccination at Concentration Camp (Camp de Septfonds, France), 1939-12-02
  - Certification by Henry Domingo, Labor Director of the Comité National Catholique de Secours aux Réfugiés de Espagne about MAJ's Skills in Radio Electronics while at Camp de Septfonds, 1939-12-09
  - Duplicate Spanish Drivers' License for MAJ, 1940-02-15
  - Letter from Henry S. Waterman (State Department), Bordeaux to MAJ Stating their Willingness to Issue a Passport and Promised Payment by the Commission Internationale d'Aide aux Enfants Réfugiés for his Passage to the U.S. if he is Released, 1940-02-21
  - Letter from Waterman to Commandent, Camp de Septfonds Requesting MAJ's Release, 1940-02-21
- Jimenez Tejeda Family -- Letters (Spanish Civil War Period), 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - MAJ Letter to MJT (Titi), HTJ, and DJT, 1939-06-02
  - MJR Letter from Dole to MJT, Barcelona, 1939-06-03
  - MJR Letter from Dole to HTJ, Barcelona, 1939-06-23
  - Letter André Barthélémy, Dole to MJT, Barcelona, 1939-06-24
  - Letter Jaime Feliubadaló, Barcelona to MJR, Dole, 1939-07-15
  - Letter André Barthélémy, Dole to Jimenez-Tejeda Family, Barcelona, 1939-07-16
  - Letter André Barthélémy, Dole to MJT, Barcelona, 1939-07-21
  - Letter from MJR, Dole to DJT, Barcelona, 1939-07-24
  - Letter from MJR, Dole to Jimenez-Tejeda Family, Barcelona, 1939-07-27
  - Letter André Barthélémy, Dole to Jimenez-Tejeda Family, Barcelona, 1939-08-02
  - Letter André Barthélémy, Dole to MJT, Barcelona, 1939-08-12
  - Letter André Barthélémy, Dole to Jimenez-Tejeda Family, Barcelona, 1939-08-17
  - MJR Letter from Dole to Jimenez-Tejeda Family, Barcelona, 1939-08-25
  - Letter André Barthélémy, Dole to MJT, Barcelona, 1939-08-31
  - MJR Letter from Dole to Jimenez-Tejeda Family, Barcelona, 1939-09-15
  - MJR Letter from Dole to MJT, Barcelona, 1939-10-16
  - MJR Letter from Dole to Jimenez-Tejeda Family, Barcelona, 1939-10-27
  - MJR Letter from Dole to MAJ, 1940-02-22
  - AJT Letter from Dole to MAJ, 1940-02-29
  - Mari? Letter from Dole to MAJ, Camp de Septfonds, France, 1940-02-29
- Jimenez Tejeda Family Photographs -- Internment/Concentration Camps Post-Spanish Civil War (France), 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 5 Photos from Dole, France Internment camp for Non-combatants – Manuel Jimenez Romance, Daniel Jimenez and Others, 1939
  - 6 Photos MAJ and Others in Gurs, France Concentration Camp, 1939-1940
- Jimenez Tejeda Family Photographs and Documents -- Spain to NYC Rescue and Move, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Receipt Funds Manuel Jimenez Tejeda to Howard Bucknell, US Consul General, 1939-08-23
  - Three Letters Howard Bucknell to Jefé Superior de Policía, Barcelona re: Delores, Fernando and Juan Stating US Citizenship and Asking for Instructions for their Safe Passage to US, 1939-12-26
  - Letter A,C, Frost, State Department to MAJ re: Repatriation of Siblings from Barcelona to NYC, 1940-07-12
  - Three Photos Originally Published in Look Magazine of MAJ Greeting his Siblings Coming from Barcelona, Spain, 1940
  - Copy of "Under the Lid of Fascist Censorship: Six Orphaned Americans Escape from Franco's Spain to Tell About the Hunger, Terrorism and Unrestin Living Under Little Fascism's Dictator" from Friday Magazine, 1940-08-23
- Jimenez Tejeda Letters (New York City), 1940 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Letter from José Baldice, Venissieux to MAJ, 1940-03-17
  - Letter from Isabel?, Barcelona to DJT, New York, 1940-10-01
  - Letter from friends, Barcelona to Jimenez Tejeda Family, 1940-10-06
  - Letter from Erini?, Barcelona to DJT, New York, 1940-10-26
  - Letter from Vincente?, Barcelona to MJT, New York, 1940
- Jimenez-Walton Photographs -- Personal, Union, 1940-1944 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Photo of MAJ and MWJ in Rose Valley, circa 1940
  - Two Photos of MWJ Swearing into the Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America (IUMSWA), circa 1943
  - Local 2 Delegation of IUMSWA at 1944 Convention
- Jimenez-Walton Correspondence, 1940-1942 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Mike Jimenez, Philadelphia to Mary Rachel Walton, New York, 1940-11-19
  - Mike Jimenez, Philadelphia to Mary Rachel Walton, New York, 1940-11-28
  - Mike Jimenez, Detroit to Mary Rachel Walton, New York, 1940-12-07
  - Mike Jimenez, New Haven, Connecticut to Mary Jimenez, Brooklyn, NY, 1942-01-22
  - Mike Jimenez, New Haven, Connecticut to Mary Jimenez, Brooklyn, NY, 1942-01-26
  - Mike Jimenez, New Haven, Connecticut to Mary Jimenez, Brooklyn, NY, 1942-02-03
  - Mike Jimenez, Washington, DC to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1942-07-30
  - Mike Jimenez, Washington, DC to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1942-08-04
  - Mike Jimenez, Washington, DC to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, August 18 or 19, 1942
  - Mike Jimenez, Washington, DC to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1942-08-25
  - Mike Jimenez, to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1942-08-29
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1942-10-01
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1942-10-07
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1942-10-17
- Jimenez-Walton Letters and Documents -- Friends, Professional, 1940-1943 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Letter R. B. Shipley, State Department, to MAJ re: Passport, 1940-06-08
  - Letter Vito Marcantonio to MAJ re: Availability, 1940-07-02
  - Letter MAJ to Ambassador William C. Bullit re: Lack of Support for Spain and Anti-fascists, 1940-08-30
  - Letter from Helen Horton to MWJ re: Delores Jimenez, 1942
  - Letter to MWJ from Unknown in Spanish, 1942-03-06
  - Letter Madelin and Sam Blitzstein to MAJ re: Friends and Move of Office of Russian War Relief, circa 1943
  - Letter MAJ to Lt. Col. Evans Carlsen, Marine Corps re: Support for Unions, 1943-06-28
  - Letter from Madelin and to MAJ re: Russian Front, 1943-09-10
  - Letter from Leslie Hutchins to MAJ with Family News, 1943-12-29
  - Letter Elizabeth Price to MAJ with Family News, 1944-01-05
  - Letter from Ellery C. Huntington, Jr., OSS to MAJ re: Commission, 1944-03-03
  - Letter from L. W. Lowman, Colonel, Airborne Division to MAJ, 1944-04-26
  - Letter and envelope from ? Amprino, Officier de Liason, OSS, Annecy, France to MAJ, in French, 1944-05-05
  - Letter from Giulio Colombo, Turino, Italy to MAJ, in Italian, 1946-03-15
- Jimenez, Michael A. -- Military, 1940-1942 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Registration Certificate, 1940-10-16
  - US Civil Service Commission Application Form 375 (Blank), 1941
  - Copy letter MAJ to General George C. Marshall Describing Skills and Experience, 1941-12-22
  - War Department Signal Corps to MAJ re: Application and Interview, 1942-01-08
  - War Department Adjutant General to MAJ re: Application, 1942-01-09
  - OSS to Local Board No. 34 (Brooklyn) re: Release of MAJ for Purpose of Enlistment, 1942-12-02
- Jimenez, Michael A. -- Military, 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - US Army North Africa to MAJ re: Appointment to 2nd Lieutenant Effective 1943-12-01, Serial Number 02055969, 1943-11-21
  - Special Orders, US Army North Africa, MAJ Promoted to 2nd Lieutenant and Assigned to OSS, WD, 2677th Hq Co Effective 1943-12-01, 1943-11-21
  - US Fifth Army to OSS Commanding Officer re: MAJ Appointment to 2nd Lieutenant Effective 1943-12-01 and Request to Discharge Effective 1943-11-30, 1943-11-28
  - MAJ US Army Enlisted Record and Honorable Discharge, 1943-11-30
  - US Army Commendation for Meritorious Service North Africa to MAJ, Technical Sergeant, for Saving Drowning Girl, Algeria, 1943-12-02
  - Special Orders, US Army 2677th Hq, MAJ Qualified Parachutist Effective 1943-11-10, 1944-01-23
  - MAJ Commendation from Commanding Colonel CWS OSS Allies Armies in Italy to Commanding Officer US Army 2677th Hq, 1944-03-29
  - OSS Allies Armies in Italy to MAJ re: Assistance with Major B. J. Smith Account, 1943-05-11
  - MAJ to OSS Italy Requesting Field Mission in Occupied Italy, 1944-05-20
  - US Army North Africa to MAJ re: Appointment to 1st Lieutenant Effective 1943-12-01, 1944-07-07
  - Special Orders US Army North Africa re: Appointment to 1st Lieutenant, 1944-07-07
  - MAJ Identification Paper from Chef de Batallion, Service de la Securite Militaire, Annecy, France re: American Detachment at Chateau-Gaillard, Haute-Savoie, 1944-12-28
  - MAJ Identification Card OSS Allied Armies in Italy as 2nd Lieutenant, MAJ Membership Card OSS Officers Club Italy, Membership Card Fifth Army Association, circa 1943-1944
- Jimenez, Michael A. -- Military, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Orders OSS European Theater re: MAJ Deployment to Field Base "F", 1945-01-09
  - Papers from French Army 7th Battalion de Chasseurs Alpins (7ème B. C. A) re: Passage for MAJ and Men to Italy and Back through the Col de la Galise, in Alps, Haute Savoie Department, 1945-01-16
  - Papers from French Army 27th (27e) Division Alpins re: Passage for MAJ and Men to Italy and Back via the "Col de l'Iséran, Bonneval, Col d'Arnase" in Alps, Haute Savoie Department, 1945-01-18
  - Letter from Prime Minister Ivanoe Bonomi of Italy to C. L. N. A. I. (Northern Committee of National Liberation) re: Praise for MAJ Support to Italian Resistance Fighters across German lines in Haute Savoie Department, 1945-02-28
  - Translation of Bonomi Letter, 1945
  - Letter of Commendation from US 6th Army Group Brigadier General to MAJ for Report on Northern Italy, 1945-03-13
  - Cover memo for 1945-03-13 Letter of Commendation from Colonel HQ 2677th Regiment OSS to MAJ, 1945-03-20
  - Papers from French Bureau de Sécurité Militaire re: Passage for MAJ of the Menthon de St. Bernard in Alps, Haute Savoie Department, Valid 1945-04-01 to 1945-05-31, 1945-03-27
  - Order US Army European Theater re: MAJ Legion of Merit "for Services in Italy from 16 January to 4 February 1945", 1945-04-30
  - MAJ Citation for Legion of Merit, 1945-04
  - US Army Mediterranean Theater Certificate of Promotion re: Promotion to Captain, 1945-05-17
  - Officer's Pay Data Card, 1945
  - 2677th Regiment OSS Clearance Procedure, 1945-05-26
  - Orders US Army Mediterranean Theater re: MAJ to U.S., 1945-05-27
  - Letter Order OSS Washington D. C. to MAJ for 30-day Leave in Moylan PA followed by Permanent Duty in Washington D.C., 1945-06-22
  - Letter Order OSS Washington D.C. to MAJ for 30-day Leave beginning 1945-06-23, 1945-06-22
  - Special Order War Department Washington D.C. re: MAJ Relieved from OSS, Assigned to Camp McQuaide Effective 1945-07-23, 1945-07-16
  - Telegram from MAJ to US War Department re: 15-day Extension of Leave and US War Department Approval via Message form to MAJ, 1945-07-19
  - Special Order US Army Service Forces Camp McQuaide re: Assignment to Hq WCPC 1958 SCU Effective 1945-07-23, 1945-07-24
  - OSS Director William J. Donovan to MAJ re: Service upon Return to Army, 1945-07-25
  - Special Order US Army Service Forces Camp McQuaide re: Assignment to Hq WCPC 1958 SCU, 1945-08-09
  - MAJ Officer Qualifications Record, 1945-08-21
  - US War Department Message form to OSS Requesting Records for MAJ and Irving Goff, 1945-08-17
  - Voucher for Reimbursement US War Department to MAJ for Expenses for Dependents' Travel, 1945
  - Memo US Army Service Forces Camp McQuaide re: Officer of the Day (MAJ – 1945-09-11), 1945-08-30